slid.es 2019-11-16

# Slides

It is Slides, Inc.'s ("Slides," "we", "our" or "us") policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect, how we use the information and how you can control what you provide us. 

This Privacy Policy also incorporates our Security Policy, our GDPR FAQ, our Cookie Policy and our Third Party Infrastructure Policy. 

### What information is collected

#### Information you provide us

Slides may collect the following personally-identifying information: 

  * contact information including name, email address, username and billing address
  * billing information including credit card details
  * interactions such as views and likes of presentations
  * preferences or settings that determine a consistent experience on our service
  * comments made on presentations
  * your internet protocol (IP) address
  * feedback or requests for support
  * user content, to the extent that you choose to input personally-identifying data as part of presentations, images, comments, and other content that you post to or through our service

The amount and type of information that Slides gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Slides to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Slides – by purchasing a paid account, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. 

#### Information we collect automatically

Like most website operators, Slides collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Slides’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Slides’ visitors use its website. From time to time, Slides may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Slides uses cookies to help Slides identify and track visitors, their usage of Slides website, and their website access preferences. Slides visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Slides website, with the drawback that certain features of the Slides website may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

#### Aggregated Statistics

Slides may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Slides may monitor the most popular decks on the Slides website. Slides may display this information publicly or provide it to others. 

### How information is used

Slides uses information it collects to deliver Slides' service to you and continuously enhance your experience. If you are a registered user of a Slides website and have supplied your email address, Slides may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Slides and our products. We primarily use our product blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. 

### With whom information is shared

Slides uses certain third-party services to enhance your user experience, collect public-information about visitors and collect and process payments securely. 

Slides discloses personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to process it on Slides’ behalf or to provide services available at Slides’ websites, and that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By using Slides’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 

Additionally, Slides may disclose personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Slides believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Slides, third parties or the public at large. 

Slides will not rent or sell personally-identifying information to anyone. 

#### Business Transfers

If Slides, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Slides goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Slides may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

### How you can control the information we collect

Slides collects personally-identifying information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Slides. Slides does not store credit card details that are entered at the time of purchase, that information is sent directly to Stripe (our payment processor) and we only store the necessary references to your account such that we can securely interact with our payment processor. You can control which information you supply at any time, with the caveat that it may prevent you from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

#### EU personal data

If you are located in the EU, United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway, Switzerland, or Iceland, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) related to your personal data, as further described below. Slides will be the controller of your personal data processed in connection with the service. 

#### Accessing, correcting, and deleting your personal data

You have certain rights with respect to your personal data, and we want to help you review and update your information to ensure it is accurate and up-to-date. 

If you have a Slides account, you can accomplish most of the following by logging into your account. For more information or any additional requests you can contact us via [privacy@slides.com](mailto:privacy@slides.com?subject=Privacy). 

  * **Access:** You can request more information about the personal data we hold about you and request a copy of such personal data.
  * **Rectification:** If you believe that any personal data we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, you can request that we correct or supplement such data.
  * **Erasure:** You can request that we erase some or all of your personal data from our systems. If you wish to erase all of your personal data, you can sign in and delete your user account from the account settings page.
  * **Portability:** You can ask for a copy of your personal data in a machine-readable format.

### How information is protected

Slides takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. Your account is protected by a password you set and are responsible for keeping safe. When entering information into our system such as passwords or financial information, all if this is done securely using SSL. 

### International privacy laws

If you are using our service from outside of the United States, please be aware that you are sending data, including personally identifying information, to the United States where our servers are located. That information may then be transferred within the United States and then transferred back out of the United States to countries outside of your residence, depending upon the type of information and how it is stored by us. Our collection, storage and use of your personal information will at all times continue to be governed by this Privacy Policy. 

### Children and our services

Our services are not directed towards children and you may not use our service if you are under the age of 13. You must also be old enough to consent for the processing of your personal data in your country. In certain countries, we may allow a parent or guardian to consent for you on your behalf. 

### How you may contact us

Slides has a "Data Protection Officer" who is responsible for matters relating to privacy and data protection. You may reach us with any inquiries or concerns with regards to this privacy policy here: 

Slides, Inc.  
Attn: Data Protection Officer  
223 Bedford Ave, PMB 518  
Brooklyn, NY 11211  

### Privacy Policy Changes

Slides may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Slides’ sole discretion. Slides encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

Effective as of 11-11-2019. View the previous version of this Privacy Policy.
